Frasier mss., 1934-2014 LMC 2962
Lilly Library
Frasier mss.
1934-2014
Lilly Library
Frasier, David K., 1951-
Anger, Kenneth
Gacy, John Wayne
Meyer, Russ, 1922-2004
LMC 2962
22 Boxes
5 folios oversize
The Frasier mss., 1934-2014, consist of David K. Frasier's research materials, drafts, and related correspondence for his encyclopedias of show-business homicide and suicide as well as his biography/bibliography of Russ Meyer. Also included is correspondence with and writings about serial killer John Wayne Gacy and filmmaker Kenneth Anger.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift: 2021
Biographical Note
David K. Frasier is a retired reference librarian and author/editor of Suicide in the Entertainment Industry, Murder Cases of the Twentieth Century, Russ Meyer: The Life and Films, and Show Business Homicides. Frasier gained an interest as a teen in show-business and entertainment crime from filmmaker and author Kenneth Anger's Hollywood Babylon, which he describes as "the very first tale of Hollywood sexcess, murder, suicide, and failed dreams." Frasier has since maintained a nearly 40-year friendship and correspondence with Anger. Around the same time, Frasier saw a double billing of Good Morning...and Goodbye! and Common-Law Cabin by Russ Meyer, a director known for his campy sexploitation films featuring large-breasted women. This discovery led Frasier to write a biography/bibliography/filmography of Russ Meyer and his works, sparking a decades-long friendship and leading to Frasier's editorial work on Meyer's autobiography, A Clean Breast. As Head of Technical Services at the Kinsey Institute, Frasier contacted serial killer John Wayne Gacy in prison to acquire his artwork for the Kinsey's collections. This led to several years of correspondence between Frasier and Gacy (and at least one visit) until Gacy's execution. More information on Frasier's complicated correspondence and acquaintance with Gacy can be found in his essay "Murder is My Beat," located in the John Wayne Gacy series of this collection.
Scope and Contents
The Russ Meyer series consists of correspondence and ephemera from Frasier and Meyer's many years of friendship, as well as materials relating to Frasier's writings about Meyer and Frasier's editorial work on Meyer's autobiography, A Clean Breast. Murder Cases of the Twentieth Century includes research materials arranged by entry, as well as related correspondence and publication materials. Suicide in the Entertainment Industry consists of research materials and photographs of subjects, including materials on unused entries and Frasier's notebook with drafts. The John Wayne Gacy series consists primarily of Frasier's correspondence with Gacy, as well as Gacy's autobiography Question of Doubt, ephemera related to Gacy, and Frasier's writings on Gacy. Show Business Homicides includes research materials and photographs arranged by subject, as well as publication materials and unused entries. The Kenneth Anger series consists mainly of correspondence between filmmaker Kenneth Anger and Frasier, including a significant volume of clippings and enclosures sent by Anger to Frasier, as well as a sizeable collection of Michael Jackson memorabilia collected by Anger after Jackson's death.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into the following series: Russ Meyer, Murder Cases of the Twentieth Century, Suicide in the Entertainment Industry, John Wayne Gacy, Show Business Homicides, and Kenneth Anger. There is some overlap between the contents of Suicide in the Entertainment Industry and Show Business Homicides, as entries were sometimes used in both works. Folder-level arrangement in Murder Cases of the Twentieth Century, Suicide in the Entertainment Industry, and Show Business Homicides reflects the creator's original organization of materials.
Entertainers; suicide; Homicide; murder; Crime; Motion picture film; Radio; Television; Music; Theater
- Russ Meyer
  - Arrow Films retrospective
    - Booklet typescript by Frasier (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "Immoral Mr. Teas" interview of Meyer by Frasier (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Russ Meyer: The Life and Films
    Scope and Contents
    Rosken optioned Life and Films. Includes DVD
    - Reviews, 3 Folders (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
      Rosken optioned Life and Films
    - Todd Rosken - correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Todd Rosken - scripts (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Roger Ebert's letter for Frasier's tenure case (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence to Frasier (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Review copy recipient list (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - A Clean Breast
    - Invoices and payments to Frasier (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Publicity (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Corrections and publishing materials, 2 Folders (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
    - Blue lines (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chronology of Frasier's work with Meyer (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - E! True Hollywood Story - Russ Meyer materials (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Frasier and Jimmy McDonough (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - "Russ Meyer: An Annotated Bibliography and Research Guide" (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Frasier and Meyer (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence with A. Lee Blackman regarding bootleg Meyer video sales (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Frasier's tribute to Anthony James Ryan (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mike Carroll - correspondence and DVDs (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "A Discussion of Lorna with Russ Meyer" by Frasier (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mockup script of Immoral Mr. Teas by Frasier (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Signed magazines featuring articles about Meyer (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Clippings about Meyer (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - French Peep Show - promotional booklet (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Photos of Meyer and Meyer's house (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "The Body Shop" - postcards (Box 1, Folder 30)
    The Body Shop was a strip club frequented by Meyer
  - Kitten Navidad - business card (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Edy Williams - photos (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Common-Law Cabin - transcript (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Erica Gavin - inscribed copy of interview in Glamour Girls (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Publicity and promotional material - Meyer's films (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Tundi promotional photos (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Raven de la Croix biography (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Meyer's funeral - photos and related material (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Meyer's will and trust (folder 1) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Meyer's will and trust (folder 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Signed Meyer VHS cassettes and cases, 2 Folders (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
    Includes Voluptuous Vixens, Beyond the Valley of the Ultravixens, Common-Law Cabin, Finders Keepers Lovers Weepers, and Good Morning...and Goodbye!
  - E! True Hollywood Story - Russ Meyer VHS tapes (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Murder Cases of the Twentieth Century
  - Crippen, Hawley Harvey (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - De Kaplany, Geza (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Einhorn, Ira (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ellis, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Heath, Neville (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hickock, Richard Eugene and Smith, Perry (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Judy, Steven (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Judd, Winnie Ruth (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hauptmann, Bruno (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Leopold, Nathan (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - List, John (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Lundgren, Jeffrey Don (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - McCollum, Ruby (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mossler, Candace (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mothershed, William James (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Nichols, Donald Boone (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Padola, Guenther (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Powell, Bernadette (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Putnam, Mark Steven (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Rattenbury, Alma and Stoner, George Percy (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Rouse, Alfred Arthur (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Rowland, Walter Graham (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Ruppert, James (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Ruxton, Buck (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Scott, Leonard Ewing (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Seddon, Frederick (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Sellers, Sean (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Severson, Karen (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Sheppard, Sam (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Simmons, Ronald Gene (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Slater, Oscar (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Snyder, Ruth and Gray, Judd (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Speck, Richard (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Steinberg, Joel (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Stutzman, Eli (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Swartz, Larry (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Tait, Robert Peter (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Taylor, Kenneth Z. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Thatcher, Colin (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Thomas, Arthur Allan (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Thompson, T. Eugene (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Thorne, Norman (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - True, Ronald (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Tucker, Karla Faye (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Umstadter, Travis (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Vaquier, Jean Pierre (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Walker, Buck (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Wallace, William Herbert (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Weger, Chester Otto (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Yukl, Charles W. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Zeigler, Thomas (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Zodiac (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Photograph and information requests (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - McFarland correspondence and corrections (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Suicide in the Entertainment Industry
  - Abingdon, William L. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Acland, Chris (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Acord, Art (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Acord, Art - photograph (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Acosta, Peter (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Adams, Everlyne (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Adams, Margaret (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Nick (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Alban, Jean Pierre (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Albertson, Arthur (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Alexander, Aleta Freile (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Alexander, Ross (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Allard, Bob (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Allen, Chet (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Charles (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Andre, Gwili (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Angeli, Pier (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Angeli, Pier - photograph (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ardell, John E. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Argov, Zohar (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Armendariz, Pedro (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Armendariz, Pedro - photograph (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Armitage, Pauline (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Arnold, Jess (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ash, Ernest A. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Auer, Norma (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Austin, Ann (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Austin, Tex (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Aye, Maryon (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Ayler, Albert (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Aylmer, David (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ayres, Dudley (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Bacon, Faith (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bacon, Faith - photograph (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Badfinger (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bainbridge, Barton (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Baker, James Robert (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Bantchevsky, Bantcho (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Baretti, Louis (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Barnes, Fred (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Barnet, Boris (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Barraco, Paul (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Barry, Don "Red" (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Barry, Don "Red" - photograph (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Barrymore, Diana (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Barron, Donna (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Barton, Arthur (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Bates, Barbara (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Bates, Edward (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Battles, Marjorie Ann (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Baucus, Frank M. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Baxter, Dale (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Beckett, Scotty (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Beckham, Tom (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Beecroft, A. A. (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Begelman, David (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Bell, Stanley (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Bellamy, Peter (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Benet, Brenda (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Bengston, Elmer L. (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Bennett, Jill (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Bergman, Mary Kay (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Best, Don (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Bettelheim, Spencer D. (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Beyfuss, Alexander (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Bing, Herman (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Birdwell, Dorothy (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Bishop, Robert Hamilton III (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Blandick, Clara (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Blaney, Mae (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Blattner, Ludwig (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Bloodgood, Clara (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Bond, Graham (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bondshu, Neil (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Borland, Adrian (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Borneman, Ernest (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bowers, John (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bowers, John - photograph (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Boyce, St. Elmo (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Boyce, Tommy (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Boyer, Charles (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Boyer, Michael Charles (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Boyle, Jack F. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bradbury, James Jr. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brady, James Kelvin (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Brand, Marlon (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Brando, Cheyenne (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Brandstatter, Eddie (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Brannon, Robert R. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Breen, Benita (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Brennan, Louis Kelso (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bright, Oliver Jay (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Brill, Peter (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Brody, Lee (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Brooke, Tyler (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Brooks, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Brower, Jay (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Susan (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Browne, John (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Bruckman, Clyde (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Buchanan, Jack (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Buchanan, Roy (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Burton, Sam J. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Bustros, Dany (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Butterell, Sam (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Cady, Jerome (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Calvert, Marguerite (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Cammell, Donald Seton (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Canada, Tressie (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Canow, William (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Capucine (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Capucine - photograph (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Carew, Arthur E. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Carlton, Rex (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Carmall, Francis J. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Carnevale, Luigi (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Carpenter, Donald (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Carr, Joseph L. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Carroll, James (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Casady, Weir (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Cassady, Eddy (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Cavanaugh, Earl (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Charle, Tamara (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Charters, Spencer (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Chavez, Dolores (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Chic, Charles (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Chubbuck, Christine (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Churchill, Frank (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Clark, Frank (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Clermont, Hannibal N. (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Cobain, Kurt (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Cohen, Herb (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Cohn, Richard (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Collins, Etta Stewart (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Collins, Sid (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Combs, Ray (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Common, Tommy (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Cooksey, Curtis (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Cooper, Courtney Ryley (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Corbaley, Maxine (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Cory, George (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Cotton, Lucy (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Cozad, Andrew M. (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Crandall, Harry M. (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Crane, Vincent (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Crash, Darby (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Creelman, James (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Criss, Sonny (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Crockett, Clarence (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Crofoot, Alan (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Croft, Lee D. E. (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Crosby, Dennis M. (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Crosby, Lindsay (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Cudahy, John P. (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Cuneo, Louis H. (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Curry, Helen (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Curtis, Ian (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Cutts, Patricia (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Dailey, Dan III (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Dalida (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Daly, Anna (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Dandridge, Dorothy (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Dane, Karl (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Dane, Karl - photograph (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Daniels, Roy G. (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Danneman, Monika (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Darvi, Bella (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Daugherty, Virgil "Jack" (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Davidson, George (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Davies, Lynette (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Davis, Peggy (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Davis, Rose (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - De Berg, Adolph (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - De Lane Lea, William (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Decker, Phelps (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Deckers, Jeanine (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Dee Jean, Delia (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Dekker, Albert (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Dekker, Albert - photograph (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Desai, Manmohan (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Desmonde, Jerry (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Dewaere, Patrick (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Dimmitt, Charles R. (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Dimsdale, Howard (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Dittrich, Fred A. (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Dixon, Mort (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Dobritch, Alexander (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Dolly, Jenny (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Donley, Katherine (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Donnelly, Cornelius (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Doonan, Patric (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Douglas, Barbara L. (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Dowling, Joan (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Drake, Lynwood C. (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Drake, Nick (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Drew, Lillian (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Dreyfuss, Henry (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Du Cella, Countess (Mary) (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Duane, Anne (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Duel, Pete (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Duel, Pete - photograph (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Duell, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Duffy, John Paul (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Dunville, T. E. (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Dupree, Maida (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Dusenbury, Will J. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Duval, Lillian Bell (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Eagels, Jeanne (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Eastman, George (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Eberhardt, Walter F. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Eccles, John B. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ecker, Murray (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Eddy, Wesley (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Edgell, Robert (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Edwards, Darrell (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Edwards, Jeannie (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Eichelberger, Ethyl (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Eisenberg, Emanuel (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Ellison, Jim (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Enslen, Neel (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Entwistle, Peg (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Entwistle, Peg - photograph of uncle's home (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Epic Soundtracks (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Erickson, Carl (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Ernst, Hugh (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Espe, Geraldine Soles (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Eustache, Jean (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Fabian, Abraham (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Fabris, Pasqual (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Falke, Charles (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Farnsworth, Richard (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Farnsworth, Richard - photograph (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Farnum, Jacqueline (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Farrar, Dorothy M. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Fay, Florence (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Felton, Earl (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Ferson, Earl H. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Ferrer, Nino (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Fillmore, Russell (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Finch, Mark (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Finley, Ned (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Finney, Fred (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Fischer, Harry C. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Fisher, Fred (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Flanders, Ed (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Flather, Charlotte Carter (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Fleck, Eugen (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Fleming, Caspar (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Fletcher, John W. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Fletcher, Bruz (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Flory, Regine (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Fluellen, Joel (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Flynn, J. Thornton (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Fonda, Frances (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Forman, Tom (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Fort, Garrett (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Fox, Grace (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Fragnne, Jacques du (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Frazier, Brenda (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Frazin, Gladys (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Freeman, Max (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - French, Janet (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Friedman, Joel (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Fritz, Ward C. (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Furst, Anton (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Gaby, Frank (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Galvin, Westberry (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Gardner, Frank (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Garroway, Dave (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Gary, Romain (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Gaston, Rosamund Pinchot (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Gates, Ivan R. (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Gatton, Danny (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Gay, Lillian (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Geare, Reginald Wyckliffe (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Geng, Nian Mei (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Ghazal, Aziz (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Giaconni, Ernesto (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Gildo, Rex (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Gillingwater, Claude (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Gillott, Jacky (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Gleason, Russell (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Gloor, Kurt (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Gobets, Mary (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Goerlitz, Ernest (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Goldberg, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Goldsmith, Arthur (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Goodbody, Buzz (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Goodman, Richard (Dickie) (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Goodrich, James (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Goodwin, Denis (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Gottlieb, Betty (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Graetz, Ebba (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Graham, Eddie (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Graham, Juliann (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Grant, Arthur J. (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Grant, Isabelle (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Grant, Shauna (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Graves, Mina Rudolph (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Gray, Laurence (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Greenacre, Fern (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Greene, Gilbert (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Greene, Winifred (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Greenfield, Louis R. (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Grey, Marion (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Guthu, Harold (Box 5, Folder 101)
    Includes DVD
  - Hagel, Robert (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Hale, Dorothy (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Hall, Jon (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Hall, Jon - photograph (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Hall-Davis, Lillian (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Halsted, Fred (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Hamburg, Perke (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Hamer, Rusty (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Hamilton, Harry Lud (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Hammell, John A. (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Hammond, Charles P. (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Hancock, Tony (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Handley, Frank (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Hanley, Evelyn (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Hanley, Michael Edward (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Hansen, Vern (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Hardwicke, Michael (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Hargett, Pauline (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Harris, Walter B. (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Harron, Robert (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Hartman, Elizabeth (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Hassall, Imogen (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Hastings, Frederick Cuyler (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Hathaway, Donny (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Haver, Phyllis (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Haver, Phyllis - photograph (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Hawke, Rohn Olin (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Hayes, Ray (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Heald, L. W. (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Held, Lillian (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Hemingway, Ernest (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Hemingway, Margaux (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Hendon, Rigsby, D. (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Henry, John (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Henshaw, Roger Dale (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Hero, Maria Itubri (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Higgins, Edgar (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hill, George William (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hill, George William - photograph (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hilliar, William J. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hoegler, Albert (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hollahan, John W. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Holland, Anthony (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hollenbeck, Don (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Holliday, Frank Jr. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Holliday, Michael (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Holman, Libby (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Hope, Adele Blood (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Hopkins, Doug (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hoppe, William H. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hopton, Harry Russell (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Horton, Murray (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Houston, Elsie (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Howard, Eandree (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Howard, George Bronson (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Howard, Irma (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Howard, Lisa (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Hudson, Alfred (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Huet, Jacqueline (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Hughes, Adelaide (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Hurst, Ronald S. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Hutchence, Michael (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Hutton, Leona (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Hyde, George (Box 6, Folder 29)